https://www.dewhurst.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Use of informationAs a user of our website you will always have control of the data we collect about you. However, there is areas of the website that will require you to provide certain information for you to be able to use or access them.   For example, our Online Ordering facility.Your title and full nameYour business detailsYour contact information including address, telephone number(s), email addressPayment detailsOther information you may need to share with us that we need to ensure we meet your requirementsWe also collect data from you to help us provide a good service, examples below:-Request a quotationRegister and setup an account with usMake a purchaseSign-up to our newsletterMake a general equiryApply for a job via the online CareersSend a general emailArrange a ReturnSite & Content PersonalisationWe will use information that you provide about yourself and your preferences to try and provide you with web content which we believe to be relevant and of interest to you.Website and Cookie InformationWe automatically collect information about the use of our website and services, such as what type of device you have and which type of internet browser or mobile device you use, whether you visited our website from another website or service and your IP address (the unique reference number that identifies your device on the internet). We use industry standard Google Analytics to give us a statistical picture of how our website is used.We also collect information using cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your browser which sometimes follow the movements of visitors on our website and tell us how our website and services are used.Lawful BasisThe legal basis on which we process your personal data when you make an enquiry with us is based on our legitimate interest to understand your needs and provide you with the best products and service we can.When you purchase from us, we may collect the following information: name, organisation, phone number, email address, address, billing address, VAT number (if applicable). If you don’t provide this information, you won’t be able to purchase from us or enter into a contract with us. In these instances, we process your personal data because it is necessary for the performance of a contract with you, or in order to take steps at your request to enter into a contract.When you send us an enquiry or purchase from us, you can opt in to receive marketing communications in relation to our products and services by ticking the relevant boxes. We will then send you the relevant marketing communications until such time that you remove your consent. In these instances, processing is performed on the basis of your consent.Marketing ChoicesLike you, we hate spam and junk mail. We will not sell your information to marketing companies. We do send out marketing emails from time to time, but they will only be sent to you where you have agreed to receive these.We also understand that you might change your mind about receiving our occasional communications. If you do not wish us to continue to contact you in this way, you can either follow the unsubscribe instructions on any of our communications or contact us by using the contact us at privacy@dewhurst.co.uk.Who we share your information withWe won’t sell your information although, like most organisations, there may be cases when we need to share information.We work with employees, partners and agents who are involved in delivering the products or services that you order. We ensure these are covered under appropriate contractual and confidentiality protections.If we were sold to another organisation, we may transfer any personal information we hold about you to that organisation as part of the sale or re-organisation.We may also share information where we are required or allowed to do so by law or if we believe that this is necessary to prevent fraud or cyber-crime or to protect the site or the rights or safety of its users or any other person.How we keep your personal information secureWe store personal information on secure servers that are managed by us and our service providers, and occasionally hard copy files that are kept in secure locations. Personal information that we store or transmit is protected by security and access controls, including username and password authentication, two-factor authentication, and data encryption where appropriate.How you can access your personal informationYou also have the right to make a request to access personal information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that data. You can also close the account you have with us for any of our websites at any time. To make an access or correction request, contact us using the contact details at the end of this policy.Retention timeWe will keep hold of your data for no longer than necessary. The length of time we retain it will depend on any legal obligations we have (such as tax recording purposes), the nature of any contracts we have in place with you, the existence of your consent or our legitimate interests as a business.If you no longer want us to use your personal information or to provide you with services, you can request that we erase your personal information. Please note that if you request the erasure of your personal information we will retain information from deleted accounts as necessary for our legitimate business interests, to comply with the law, prevent fraud, collect fees, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with investigations, enforce the terms of service and take other actions permitted by law. The information we retain will be handled in accordance with this policy.Information you make public or give to othersIf you make your personal information available to other people, we can’t control or accept responsibility for the way they will use or manage that data. There are lots of ways that you can find yourself providing information to other people, like when you post a public message on a forum thread, share information via social media, or make contact with a third-party whether via our website or directly via email.Before making your information publicly available or giving your information to anyone else, think carefully as this privacy policy will not apply.How you can contact usIf you have any questions about our privacy practices or the way in which we have been managing your personal information, please contact us in writing at Dewhurst UK, Unit 9, Hampton Business Park, Hampton Road West, Feltham, TW13 6DB, United Kingdom or email us privacy@dewhurst.co.ukDewhurst UK Privacy Policy V1 23rd May 2018
Dewhurst UK Unit 9 Hampton Business Park Hampton Road West Feltham TW13 6DB t: +44 (0)20 8744 8200 f: +44 (0)20 8744 8299 info@dewhurst.co.ukAccessoriesAuxiliariesDestination ControlDisplaysEncoders & SpeechFixturesHidden LegendsKey SwitchesKeypadsLantens & GongsPushbuttonsUS1 Touch PanelConnect with us on social media
Facebook
Twitter
© 2020 Dewhurst UK – All Rights Reserved Registered in England and Wales No. 6834598Sitemap | Privacy Policy | Terms & ConditionsDewhurst UK Unit 9 Hampton Business Park Hampton Road West Feltham TW13 6DBt: +44 (0)20 8744 8200 f: +44 (0)20 8744 8299 info@dewhurst.co.uk Sitemap | Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions© 2020 Dewhurst UK – All Rights Reserved. Registered in England and Wales No. 6834598
MenuCategoriesAccessoriesAuxiliariesDestination ControlDisplaysDot Matrix DisplaysLCD DisplaysAccessoriesFixturesHidden LegendsHygiene PlusKey SwitchesKeypadsLanterns & GongsPushbuttonsStandardHygiene PlusJumboTransportUS1 Touch PanelSwitching RangeHomeBrowse AllOrder OnlineDesign ServiceProjectsAboutAbout DewhurstJob VacanciesPolicies and CertificatesOnline Ordering & ReturnsPrivacy PolicyLegal InformationContact Us We use cookies to improve your experience on our website. By browsing this website, you agree to our use of cookies. More info Accept
